ミーン　ミンミン…
≫チリン　チリン（自転車のベル）
≫（不破真広）吉野！
Yoshino!
俺　愛花　送っていくから。
I'm taking Aika home.
（滝川吉野）そのまま　サボるなよ。
Just don't skip class.
次　遅刻したら
単位やばいんだから。
You won't have enough credits to pass if you miss one more.
うん。　まあ　なんとかなるって。
It'll work out.
じゃあな。
ああ。
Later.
Yeah.
じゃあね　愛花ちゃん。
See you around, Aika-chan.
Couldn't you at least give him the time of day?
挨拶ぐらい返してやれよ。
（愛花）真広には関係ありません。
Mind your own business, Mahiro.
ふっ。　そこまで嫌ってやるなよ。
I don't get why you hate him so much.
Like, he might not be a good guy, but he's not that bad.
まあ　いいヤツでもないけど
悪いヤツでもないぞ。
（愛花）
中庸気取りの狡猾なヤツです。→
He's just a con artist pretending to be a nice guy.
ああいう人は　平気で　うそをつく。
The kind of guy who could lie with a straight face.
はぁ…　厳しいな。
That's harsh.
「世の中の関節は
外れてしまった」。
The time is out of joint;
（愛花）
「ああ　なんと呪われた因果か」。
O, cursed spite...
The time is out of joint;
「世の中の関節は外れてしまった。→
ああ　なんと呪われた因果か→
O, cursed spite...
それを直すために
生れついたとは！」。
That ever I was born to set it right!
Episode 1
The Mage
in the Barrel
Damn it, Samon. This was your plan?
（葉風）おのれ　左門　謀ったな。
（葉風）なるほど。
安物のサンダルにワンピースで→
Bravo.
Now I'm stranded on an island
孤島に置き去りにされたわけか。
with some cheap sandals and a sundress.
（葉風）パンツ一丁で
放り出されなかった分→
I guess it's better than being stuck here
with nothing but my underwear.
少しは　敬意を払われたらしいが→
But I can't even use magic in this state...
さすがの私も
これでは　ろくに魔法を使えんな。
（部下）左門殿。
（左門）ん？
Master Samon.
あれで　姫様を
封じられたのでしょうか？
Is this really enough to stop the princess?
あの島では　魔法を発動するに→
On this island,
she won't be able to acquire the offerings she needs to use magic.
必要な供物は手に入らん。
さすれば
姫様とて　ただの娘と変わりない。
As such, the princess is no different than an ordinary girl.
（哲馬）では　姫様は…。
（左門）ああ。　あの島で骨となる。
So the princess...
Yes, she will perish on that island.
（葉風）左門のことだ→
That's Samon for you.
島を見えなくする結界は
張ってあるだろう。→
He probably put up a barrier to make the island invisible, too.
外部に助けを求めるのも
ままならない。→
I won't be able to seek help from outside.
まさに　絶海の孤島か…。
Guess I'm stranded in the middle of nowhere.
だが　左門　安心するなよ！
Look here, Samon! You better watch your back!
私は　鎖部葉風！
一族史上　最強の魔法使い！
I'm Kusaribe Hakaze,
the strongest mage ever born into our clan!
貴様の野望　必ず　くじいてみせ…。
I'll put an end to your ambitions—
（葉風）とりあえずは
食料を確保しないといかんな…。
Guess I should gather some food first...
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（アナウンサー）今回の国防軍による
大規模な陸上演習は→
The Defense Force's held a large-scale drill recently,
Eat all your celery, too!
Promise to do it.
aimed at protecting the most remote islands.
離島の防衛を想定して
行われました。→
The Ministry of Defense made a statement on the drill,
防衛省によりますと
この演習には→
情報共有や
指揮統制能力を強化するための→
which included new tanks equipped with a C4I system to facilitate intelligence sharing,
Ｃ４Ｉシステムを装備した…。
as well as command and control measures...
Messages Received
From: Girlfriend
Subject: Tomorrow
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
（心の声）≪「明日のデート
楽しみにしています。→
"Looking forward to our date tomorrow.
今度すっぽかしたら許しません」≫
If you stand me up again, I'll never forgive you."
Such combined arms exercises are unprecedented.
Defense Force's Large-Scale Onshore Drill
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（アナウンサー）連携を重視した
訓練を行うのは　今回が初めて…。
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]　さあ　今週も検証を…。
ピッ（リモコン操作音）
Let's see what we have—
Rumors Around Town
Carrots Growing in Asphalt
Dog with Human Face Spotted!
Balls That Roll Uphill
Flying Pineapple Spotted
Elderly Man Makes Clouds Disappear
≪約束なんてものに
どれほどの重さがあるんだろう≫
How much weight does a simple promise carry?
ねえ　吉野って　割とよくね？
Hey, do you think Yoshino's cute?
I guess...
まあね。
真広いなけりゃ　ただの人だし。
But without Mahiro around, he's just another guy.
≪顔はいいんだし
とりあえず　いっとけば？
He's so fine. Why don't you go for it?
≫でもさ　彼女いるってうわさ
聞いたんだけど…。
I heard a rumor that he has a girlfriend...
いるよ。
ん？
I do.
Huh?
≪ええ～!?
≪今のって　うちらに言った？
Was he talking to us?
Who does he think he is?
≪超何様！　上から目線!?
≪うう～！
Does he think he's better than us?
Takigawa,
滝川。　不破から
その後　連絡もないのか？
have you heard anything from Fuwa?
もう　１か月だろ？
はい。　まあ→
It's been a month already.
True.
Well, if he isn't dead, he must be out there somewhere.
死んでなければ生きてますよ。
そんな適当な…。
How can you say that?
まあ　幼なじみのお前が言うなら
大丈夫なんだろうが→
I guess if it's his old friend talking that way, he must be all right.
But he disappeared without even notifying the school.
退学届　出して
いきなり消えたからな。
あいつのことだ→
And it is Fuwa...
He seems like the kind who'd cause enough trouble to make the papers.
何か新聞に載るような事件を
起こしそうでな。
You're right.
そうですね。
えっ？
What?
生きていれば　今頃
誰かを殺してるかもしれませんね。
If he's alive, he'd probably be killing someone right about now.
≪もし
約束に重さがあるのなら…≫
If promises carry weight...
≫吉野→
Yoshino!
All by yourself, eh?
お前　一人か？　ああ？
厄日だな　どうにも。
This just isn't my day.
５人か。
Five, huh?
ファイト！　ファイオー！
≫（５人）ははははっ。
Feels pretty light.
手応えねぇの。
よっ。
How much is in there?
おい　いくら入ってる？
おっ！→
He's got quite a bit.
≫結構持ってるじゃねぇの。
≫じゃ　行くか　ゲーセン。
Let's hit the arcade, then.
うん…　やっぱり無理だ。
Again?
I can't do it.
I can't take on five guys at once.
何人も相手になんて…。
でも…。
But...
≪でも　真広となら…≫
But if Mahiro was here...
（２人・回想）((ん？))
（愛花）((１５人も相手になんて→
Fifteen in a row?
Even a child would know to run away.
逃げた方がいいことぐらい
子供でも分かるでしょう))
Fights aren't about numbers...
((ケンカは数じゃねぇよ))
((それに　吉野もいたしな
囲まれたって楽勝だ))
Besides, Yoshino was with me.
Even though we were surrounded, it was easy.
So in other words, this is all Yoshino-san's fault.
((つまり　吉野さんが
すべて悪いんですね))
((ええっ!?　僕は被害者だよ！))
What? I'm the victim here!
((真広に巻き込まれて
しかたなく…))
I was dragged into Mahiro's mess, so—
((なら　一人で逃げればいい))
((ははっ))
Then you should have fled alone.
((真広を見捨てるわけには
いかないじゃないか！))
I couldn't just abandon Mahiro—
Are you stupid?
（愛花）((バカですか))
((あなたが逃げれば　真広も
勝ち目がないから逃げますよ))
Not even Mahiro is stupid enough to sit there and take all those guys on alone.
((今更　被害者ぶる方が
よほど卑劣です))
Acting like a victim makes you look even worse.
Hey, now...
((お前な…))
((みんな言ってますよ→
Everyone says it.
If not for Takigawa Yoshino,
滝川吉野さえいなければ→
不破真広は　とっくに殺されてるか
警察に捕まってるのにって))
the police would've killed or arrested Fuwa Mahiro by now.
((あなたが悪いんです))
And it's your responsibility.
((すべては　あなたの罪))
This is all your fault.
≪なあ　真広→
Hey, Mahiro...
お前が求めているものは
手に入りにくいうえに→
Acquiring what you want isn't just difficult...
It's also trivial.
つまらないものだ≫
≪たとえ手に入ったって→
Even if you got what you want,
お前を幸せにするもんじゃない≫
it wouldn't make you happy.
（山本）君が　不破真広君？
Are you Fuwa Mahiro?
また真広…　か？
Mahiro again?
Excuse me, I am Evangeline Yamamoto.
（山本）失礼。
私は　エヴァンジェリン山本。→
My friends call me Fräulein Yamamoto.
親しい人には　フロイライン山本と
呼ばれている→
Unemployed, twenty-eight years old.
無職の２８歳。
怪しい者じゃないから。
I'm not a shady character.
Everything about you is shady.
いやいや
丸ごと全部　怪しいですって。
（山本）君のプロフィールは？
滝川吉野　高２。
And what's your profile?
Takigawa Yoshino, a sophomore.
What's your relationship to Fuwa Mahiro?
（山本）
不破真広君とは　どういう関係？
He and I go way back.
つきあいだけは長いですね。
And that's enough for you to visit his family's plot?
（山本）それだけで
お墓参りまでするかな。→
Have you heard from Mahiro recently?
真広君と　最近　連絡は？
Not a word since he disappeared a month ago.
ひと月前にいなくなって
それきりです。
本当？
本当…　あっ！
Really?
Really...
Sorry, but this is important.
悪いけど
問題は　差し迫っているの。
≪いきなり突きつけられる銃…
リアリティーがなさすぎる≫
A gun suddenly shoved in my face...
This is totally surreal.
≪でも…≫
But...
（山本）２週間前　ある地域で→
Two weeks ago,
a young man in his late teens was seen in a certain area.
１０代後半とおぼしき少年が
目撃された。→
One week ago,
そして１週間前
同一と思われる少年が→
an individual thought to be the same boy was seen elsewhere.
別の地域でも。→
Both areas are now under quarantine and entrance is strictly prohibited.
どちらの地域も
現在　立ち入り禁止の厳重封鎖中。
待ってください。
そんなこと　ニュースでも…。
Hold on...
The news never mentioned that—
（山本）２番目の地域で　少年は→
In the second area,
the boy saved someone's life.
死の危険にあった人間を
１人　助けている。→
そのとき　名を尋ねられて少年は→
When asked his name, the boy called himself
不破真広と名乗った。
Fuwa Mahiro.
おっしゃってることの
ほとんどが謎ですけど…→
I don't understand anything you're saying...
あいつは　人助けなんて
するタイプじゃないですよ。
He really isn't the type to rescue somebody.
親友が　ひどい言いぐさね。
事実　あいつは　ひどいんです。
That's a terrible thing to say about a friend.
He's a pretty terrible person.
Even when dealing with a beautiful girl?
相手が　きれいな女の子でも？→
そうね　１５歳くらいの…。
Say, around fifteen years old?
No, he might've saved her.
なら　助けたかもしれません。
そういう子が　真広君の好み？
Does she sound like his type?
Mahiro had a little sister.
真広には　妹がいましたから
似た子を見ると→
If he saw someone who looked like her, he wouldn't've been able to leave.
放っておけなかったのかも
しれません。
あいつは　愛花ちゃんを
何より大事にしてましたから。
He treasured Aika-chan more than anything.
（山本）
大事にしてた？　どうして過去形？
Treasured?
Past tense?
She now rests under that gravestone.
彼女は今　その下です。
Yoshino, why did Aika have to die?
((吉野
どうして　愛花は殺された？))
((警察の言うとおりだろ))
It's probably like the police said.
((金銭目的の何者かに　家に…))
Someone broke in, looking for money—
((そういうことを
聞いているんじゃない))
You know what I mean.
((愛花は　普通に生活してた…
あの日まで))
Until that day, Aika lived a normal life.
((なのに　どうして　こんなふうに
死ぬと決められたんだ？))
Why did she have to die this way?
((そのうえ
いまだに　犯人は捕まってない))
And the killer even got away.
We still don't know that for sure.
((まだ分からない))
((事件から１０か月→
It's been ten months and they don't have any leads.
手がかり一つ　つかめていない))
Nothing left behind...
((遺留物はない　目撃者もない
犯人が　単独か複数かも→
No witnesses...
They don't even know if the killer was acting alone.
割り出せてない))
((だから　まだ…))
We just don't know.
The task force hardly does anything anymore.
((捜査本部も
ほとんど動かなくなった))
There's no chance that the case will move forward.
((これから先
事件が進展する可能性はない))
It's absurd!
((くっ…　辻褄が合わない))
It doesn't make sense...
Isn't absurdity part of the human condition?
((そこが　人の世の奥ゆかしさ
というやつじゃないか？))
You don't even give a shit, do you?
((他人事か))
Well, I guess Aika never did like you...
((まあ　お前は
愛花に　相当嫌われてたからな))
So, how would you handle such absurdity?
((で　その不合理を
お前は　どうするんだ？))
((犯人を自力で見つけて
自力で裁くのか？))
Find her killer and punish them yourself?
((ああ　そうだな))
Yeah, that's it...
((どんな手を使っても
辻褄を合わせてやる))
I'll do whatever it takes for everything to make sense again!
なるほどね。
I understand.
ううっ！
本当に　何も知らない？
You really don't know anything?
≪えっと…　どうする？≫
What should I do?
蝶…。
何？
A butterfly.
What?
いえ　アゲハ蝶が飛んでるんです。
それがどうしたのよ!?
Nothing, a swallowtail butterfly just flew by...
What of it?!
アゲハ蝶は
サナギで　冬を越すはずです。
Swallowtails spend winter in cocoons.
雪降ってるんですよ!?
It's snowing...
A single butterfly could just be an anomaly—
１匹ぐらい　何かの
間違いだってことあるでしょ…。
そんな…。
That's impossible...
バシッ！
（山本）うっ！
うっ…。
（山本）おあいにくさま→
Unfortunately for you,
銃は１丁じゃないの。
I have more than one gun.
≫ドカッ！
ああ？
人の家の墓の前で何してやがる。
Who the hell is this defiling my sister's grave?
真広!?
Mahiro...
Mahiro, where did you come from?
真広…　お前　どこから？
Over there.
あっちだ。
Over there...
あっちって…。
だから　飛んできたんだよ。
I flew here.
Huh?
はあ!?
それより　あの女は何者だ？
Anyway, who the hell is this?
Twenty-eight and unemployed, she's Fräulein Yamamoto-san.
２８歳　無職の
フロイライン山本さんだ。
Are you kidding me?
なんの冗談だよ？
山本さんも→
I doubt Yamamoto would want to hear that from some flying kid.
空飛ぶお前に
言われたくないと思う。
I just followed these guys.
こいつらを追ってきたんだ。
はっ！　真広！
Mahiro!
バキュン！
What was your plan if that had hit me?
当たったらどうしたんだ。
So, Fuwa Mahiro, you really did meet with a mage.
不破真広…　やはり君は
魔法使いに会っているのね。
魔法使い!?
あんた　政府の人間か？
A mage?
Do you work for the government?
（山本）
残念。　ただのボランティア。→
Unfortunately, I'm just a volunteer.
Do you think bureaucrats and politicians believe in magic?
役人や政治家が
魔法を信じると思う？
Answer me!
答えなさい！　あなたは
黒鉄病と　どう関わっているの!?
What is your connection to the black iron syndrome?
このままだと日本は滅びかね…。
だから　なんだよ！
At this rate, Japan will—
What's your problem?
バキッ！
うっ！
ボゥン！
くっ…。
ゼロ距離でも効かないか！
Not even at point-blank range?!
いいぜ　その強気なとこ。
I like your spirit...
でも　今は寝てろよ！
But for now, rest a while.
ふぅ…　さて　行くか。　ん？
Well, let's go.
何か言いたいことでもあんのか？
ありすぎて→
Was there something you wanted to say?
There's so much I want to say, I have no idea where to start.
どこから手をつけていいか
分からない。
Then keep your mouth shut.
だったら　黙っておけよ。
おい　待てよ　真広！
Hey...
Wait, Mahiro!
おい！
≪ドカーン
Hey!
この町も終わりだな。
あっ。
This city is done for.
大丈夫ですか!?
ほっとけ。
Are you okay?
Leave him.
もう金属化が始まってる。
えっ　金属化？
He's already beginning to metallicize.
What? Metallicize?
ガタン！
あっ！
あの女が言ってた
黒鉄病ってやつだ。
It's the syndrome she was talking about.
黒鉄病…。
The black iron syndrome...
硬い…。
Like a statue...
黒鉄病→
The black iron syndrome...
生物を金属化する呪的現象だよ。
It's a psychic phenomenon that turns all organic life into metal.
It's not a real illness,
病気じゃないが　状況だけ見れば
たちの悪い伝染病だな。
but it looks like some kind of horrible, infectious disease.
すでに３つ以上の地域で
同じことが起こってる。
The same thing already happened in three or so regions.
政府は　必死に隠しているが
いつまでもつか。
The government's doing what they can to hide it, but they won't be able to forever.
ここらも
何か理由つけて封鎖されるぞ。
They'll think up some reason to quarantine this area, too.
あの人が言ってた地域封鎖って…。
Then those barricades she was talking about...
あっ…　僕らは大丈夫なのか？
ああ。
Will we be okay?!
Yeah.
いちばん影響のあるときに
俺の近くにいたからな。　ん？
When the syndrome's effects hit their peak, you were with me.
あの女にやられたか？
いや　うちの３年の…。
Did she do that to you?
No, it was some seniors...
そんな話　今はいいから。
That isn't important right now!
Those guys again? They never learn.
また　あいつらか。
懲りないヤツらだな。
教えてくれ　真広
一体　何が起こっている？
Tell me, Mahiro...
What's going on?
あの女も言ってただろ→
She mentioned it, too...
It's magic.
魔法さ。
えっ？
The family that's using it has this moronic ambition...
それを扱う一族が
バカな野望を抱いたんだ。
In order to gain greater power,
より大きな力を得ようと→
they're trying to awaken something
目覚めさせてはいけないものを
目覚めさせようとしている。
that must never be awakened.
（男たち）戻れ　戻れ　戻れ　戻れ→
Return, return, return, return, return.
戻れ。
ガシャン　ガシャン
（男たち）戻れ　戻れ　戻れ→
Return, return, return, return, return.
戻れ　戻れ　戻れ　戻れ→
戻れ　戻れ　戻れ。
黒鉄病は　ただの前触れだ。
The black iron syndrome is simply a harbinger.
Once it awakens, Japan—
そいつが目覚めれば
日本はおろか→
世の中すべてが　ひっくり返る。
no, the entire world'll be turned upside-down.
≪変な感じだ≫
This doesn't feel right...
Feels like I'm in a strange dream, listening to Mahiro speak...
≪絵空事みたいな景色と
真広の言葉≫
そんなバカな連中を
止められるヤツが一人だけいる。
Only one person is capable of stopping those idiots.
The family heiress and the most powerful mage known to man,
その一族の姫にして
史上最強の魔法使い→
鎖部葉風。
Kusaribe Hakaze.
≪そのすべてが…→
Yet for some reason,
I believe every word...
なぜだろう
こんなにも信じられる≫
史上最強のって　お前→
The most powerful?
Then are you that mage's apprentice or something?
魔法使いの弟子にでも
なったつもりか？
弟子だって？
Apprentice?
俺が手を貸してやってるのさ。
ん？
Well, I'm helping her out.
（葉風・通信）おい　真広
これは　公平な取り引きだ。→
Hey, Mahiro...
This is a fair trade.
恩を着せられる筋合いはない。
You have no right to imply that I owe you any favors.
You say that now, Hakaze,
そうは言っても　葉風
俺がいなくて困るのは→
but you're the one in trouble without me...
（通信）お前だろ。
（葉風）ほう。
Oh?
So you're saying you don't need me
貴様の妹を殺した犯人を→
私が見つけてやらなくとも
いいというのか？
to locate your sister's killer anymore?
Hey, where did you get that doll?
おい　その人形は!?
（葉風・通信）誰かいるのか？
Is someone else there?
ああ。　こいつは…。
≫ドーーン！
Yeah, he's—
いつものが来る。　今度は海だ。
It's coming again. From the sea this time.
Got it.
（葉風・通信）
分かった。　方角を正確に測れ。
Tell me its exact origin.
あっ　真広！
Mahiro!
１か月前
俺は　砂浜に流れ着いてた→
One month ago,
I found a glass bottle washed up on the beach.
ガラス瓶を見つけた。　中には
この人形と板切れが入っていた。
Inside was the doll and a piece of wood.
そこには　文字が書かれていた。
A message was written on it.
"If you believe in magic
「魔法を信じ　魂と引き換えでも
かなえたい願いがあるなら→
and would trade your soul to have one wish granted,
この人形に　釘を打て」。
hammer a nail into this doll."
（葉風）いかに島を隠しても
海は　世界とつながっている。→
Even though this island is concealed,
the ocean is still connected to the rest of the world.
海流研究や海での遭難者が使う
情報伝達法→
The communication method used by oceanographers and castaways...
瓶詰のメッセージだ。　無人島でも
瓶くらい漂流物で手に入る。→
A message in a bottle.
Even on a deserted island, I can find a bottle among the driftwood.
あとは
中身を詰めた　それを流し→
Once I cast my message out to sea,
都合のいい者に
拾われるかどうかだったが…→
I just had to hope the right person would find it.
私の運は　やはり強い。
Guess I have some good luck, after all.
左門
パンツ一丁でも　私は手ごわいぞ。
Samon,
even in my underwear, I'm still pretty tough.
それで　孤島の魔法使いと
話せる魔法が発動した。
With that, I was able to communicate with the mage on an isolated island.
And then we made a deal.
そして　俺たちは取り引きをした。
それが　さっきの…。
So that's who that was...
In exchange for my help,
俺が手を貸す　そのかわり→
愛花を殺した犯人を
魔法とやらで見つけてみせろとな。
I told her to use her magic to find Aika's killer.
Aika's murder made no sense.
愛花が殺されたのは不合理だ。
魔法も不合理だ。
Magic doesn't make sense, either.
なら
二つをぶつければ　辻褄が合う。
Maybe two wrongs do make a right.
I will kill Aika's murderer with my own hands.
愛花を殺したヤツを
この手で殺してやれる。
I believe it...
≪すべてを信じられる≫
≪だけど…≫
But...
そういや　お前ん家の親は
隣町に働きに出てるんだったな。
By the way,
your parents are working in the next city over, right?
なら　セーフか。
えっ？　あっ　ああ。
They should be safe, then.
Huh? Y-Yeah...
彼女は大丈夫なのか？
えっ？
Is your girlfriend okay?
ああ…。　ここにはいない。
そっか。
Yeah...
She isn't here.
All right.
僕につきあってる子がいるって
お前　知っていたのか。
How did you know that I was seeing someone?
Oh, someone mentioned it.
ああ。　どいつだかが話してた。
≪すべてが狂ってる≫
This is crazy...
見ろ　吉野→
Look, Yoshino...
俺らが止めようとしているもの
その力の一部だ。
That's a part of what we're trying to stop!
（男たち）戻れ　戻れ…。
Return, return, return, return.
Return, divided fruit!
（左門）
今こそ戻れ　分かたれし果実。→
樹の中の樹　大樹の中の大樹→
Greatest of all trees, which raises itself above all others...
Return, return, return, return, return.
美しき絶園の樹に！
Return to your beautiful Tree of Exodus!
（男たち）美しい　美しい→
Beautiful, beautiful. Fruit, fruit. Beautiful...
果実　果実。　美しい…。
こんなの…→
What the...
もう　とっくに世界は
おかしくなってるんじゃないか？
When did the whole world go insane, exactly?
I don't care if this world crumbles to ashes.
この世が　バラバラになろうと
かまいやしない。
だが　吉野→
However, Yoshino...
I'll save it anyway!
俺が世界を救ってやるよ！
≪ああ　「世の中の」…≫
The time...
「世の中の関節は外れてしまった」。
The time is out of joint.
（愛花）
((中庸気取りの狡猾なヤツです。→
He's just a con artist pretending to be a nice guy.
The kind of guy who could lie with a straight face.
ああいう人は
平気で　うそをつく))
((はぁ…　厳しいな))
That's harsh.
（愛花）
((そして　私も　うそをつく))
And I'm a liar, too.
Messages Received
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
Looking forward
to our date tomorrow. If you stand
me up again, I'll never forgive you.
The time is out of joint.
「世の中の関節は外れてしまった。→
O, cursed spite...
ああ　なんと呪われた因果か」。
That ever I was born to set it right!
「それを直すために
生れついたとは！」。
Mahiro,
（愛花）真広→
what does a kiss feel like?
キスとは　どういう感じが
するものなのですか？
You don't feel happiness or sadness when you're dead.
死んだ人間は
喜びも悲しみもしない。
The promise of tomorrow won't ever come.
永遠に来ない明日の約束。
Hakaze, you'd better keep your end of the bargain.
葉風　約束は守ってもらうぞ。
Can you trust Takigawa Yoshino enough to give him a talisman?
（葉風）滝川吉野…
魔具までくれてやって→
信用できるのか？
取り引きしませんか？
Let's make a deal.
I will kill Aika's murderer with my own hands!
愛花を殺したヤツを
この手で殺すのをな！
This is where it all began.
Episode 2
He Said
She Was Quite Beautiful
ここが　すべての始まりの場所。